This is the chaotic time of
spontaneous gangs.
In order to scramble for territory...
they are not afraid
to purge each other...
despite the rules.
Butcher...
slaughter...
to survive.
Until the formation of four forces.
These four hold hundreds of juniors
under their command...
creating a balance in the underworld
during the time.
They are known as:
Cuong...
Area: Cho Lon - Weapon: Chopper
Business: Protection, loaning.
Hao...
Area: Float Market - Weapon: Scimitar
Business: Protection, smuggling.
Chan...
Area: Cau Muoi Market - Weapon: Ice saw
Business: Protection, restaurants.
Hung.
Area: Night Market - Weapon: Pig chopper knife
Business: Smuggling, prostitute.
UNTIL ONE DAY...
Hey, who keeps the cigarette pack?
I keep it.
- Give me, I'll give it back to him later.
- Here!
You keep, not me.
- Wait, I didn't keep it.
- You keep...
Attack!
Don't touch my bros.
Gotta leave now!
They're all gone. Stop acting cool.
2 - A SCAR IS A BEAUTIFUL TATTOO
Why did you guys come to this place?
To give this back to you.
We wouldn't dare to "smoke" these things…
You can give me back later!
Hey...
we've just saved you!
Nobody asked you to!
Holy moly!
Hey, Hung!
Let's talk a little bit.
Thank you, fellas.
How is Big Brother?
He's fine.
Why did you hide such cool friends?
Help yourself.
His pals are also my pals.
Thanks.
Wanna follow me to earn some cash?
What job is it?
Join our Cho Lon gang.
Oh…thanks for the offer...
but some dude told me
not to get involved in gangsters.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got work to do.
There are three of us.
Next time please offer three cigarettes.
Our gang needs people like them.
How about you stay here
permanently for convenience?
You're battered and scarred every day.
I stopped by yesterday...
but I didn't see you here.
Oh, I was visiting my dad.
Done!
Is your body a place to consign scars?
I didn't want to be like this.
I'm sorry...
for always making you
see those hideous scars.
I'm used to it!
My dad once told me...
for men, a scar is a beautiful tattoo.
Gosh, are you really
thinking of staying here?
Hello ma'am!
Ice delivery!
Alright, here you go.
- Yes.
- Ok!
Ba, park the bike
and then come wash the dishes.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Ok.
Ba!
Remember to wash them thoroughly!
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
I'll deliver tomorrow at the same hour.
Hello?
Ma'am!
Alrigh. I'm in a traffic jam.
I'm coming now.
Okay.
[BLOOD BIOCHEMISTRY ANALVSIS RESULT187]
Long, wait for me!
Yes?
Dad gave you… / No, mom!
Please remember to take care of yourself.
I'm off now.
Okay, get going.
You're too late!
The ice has melted already.
I'll only pay half the price.
I'm sorry, the traffic was heavy.
Ma'am...?
You broke almost all of my dishes!
Damn it!
We only have two packets
of instant noodles left...
and the rat nibbled half a packet.
It's okay. Half a packet
for each of us is still fine.
Long! Come and eat!
Understand for the rat!
C'est la vie!
We're running out of food?
We still have the duck.
Are you insane?
Eat noodles!
Just kidding!
How's your job?
Really good.
How about you?
Same with Ba.
And you?
Same with you two.
Hey!
Should we ask Hung?
He's been here for a long time anyway.
He probably knows
a wide range of occupations.
Damn you, bitch!
Stop right there!
How dare you run away from me?
They are all losers!
Are you cracked? We lost.
You talk too much.
Unlucky is unlucky.
Bullshit!
Come get your fish.
Hurry!
The slowest takes the smallest.
How lucky, it's almost ready.
Hung!
Your arms okay?
Doesn't matter! That's nothing for me.
Yeah, you're right.
Damn it asshole!
Jeez, it doesn't hurt that much.
Hey, to celebrate today's victory...
I will form a guild called
"Four Great Heroes".
I'll be the Master!
I'll bail.
Yo, I'm with Ba.
I'm with them two.
Bastards!
Hey!
I don't regret being born
in this life to meet you guys.
But I do.
Cut the jokes!
Now, let's use these fishes
to replace wine.
The fastest gets the biggest.
I'll get this one.
This one's mine.
- This one's mine.
Brothers for life!
- We live and die together!
Cheers!
The important thing is,
what do you guys want to do?
So, do you know of any jobs...
that are both honest and well-paid?
Holy crap!
Honest and well-paid?
These two never stick together.
Yes.
There is me.
I'm honest and good-hearted.
Good-hearted but no money.
No offense but...
my dad told me
to find a job that earns...
an honest penny and also…
If you want to take care of your dad...
then get rid of your dignity first.
Hung, do you remember?
Brothers for life.
We live and die together.
I never forget that.
Could you pretend to
take us out for some meals?
Damn you asshole!
I'mma beat you with this slipper…
always thinking about food.
Hung, let's go!
What?
- Fine.
- Let's go!
Should we eat instant noodles tonight, Ba?
Quit it. We'll be full of
noodle soup by then.
Could you take us out
for dining like this again?
Like, every day?
I really respect you.
My God!
Sir, make me four bowls of noodle soup.
- You got it.
- Just three bowls, sir.
What? Four or three?
Oh…you?
Huh?
Three bowls of noodle soup…
then bailed.
Sir, let me pay…
Are you nuts?
This is not the right time to be courteous.
But clearly, we haven't paid him
three bowls of noodle soup.
Put aside your dignity.
It's my money, I'll do what I want.
Sir, I'll pay for three bowls of
noodle soup the other day.
It was 100.000 VND in total.
Sir, let us eat first,
we'll talk about this later.
Okay, three bowls?
Yes.
Just let me pay half of it first!
Don't be silly!
Stop it. I almost forgot the taste of meat!
Look at him!
Oh. What a coincidence!
Too many things to handle that day...
I couldn't treat you guys well.
It's on me today.
Oh, you don't have to…
Sir!
Make me three bowls of pork bone stew!
Ok!
So...
have you considered my offer?
If you join my gang...
you won't have to
worry about meals anymore.
Thank you, but we can still handle it.
I don't ask you to kill or rob...
just help us with some small errands.
I can pay you well.
Sir!
Give me three more bowls of ham hocks!
Ok!
That's nice bro!
Gotta appreciate his generosity...
or we're gonna be punished in hell.
Oh, here!
Thanks.
Okay.
So?
Have you eaten enough
to think more clearly?
Thank you...
but gangsters are not our things.
Suit yourself.
Check, please!
Okay.
Let me pay for this.
It's on me.
200.000 VND in total.
You dropped the money… - Oh.
It's a bit dirty now, would you take it?
As long as it's real money.
A bit dirty is not an issue!
Dirty money is still money.
Its value remains unchanged.
The same with how others perceive you...
doesn't affect your worth.
Do all gangsters have
such a philosophic way of saying?
No.
I think he means we should be clean.
If you need anything,
just find me at Cho Lon.
Okay.
We're full now.
Take us to get some jobs, would you?
Yeah right.
Ok, let's go!
But it should be decent.
Sure!
And very okay!
Do come in.
How old are you, sweety?
I…am 28…
You're 12 years younger than me.
What?
You're so handsome, sweety.
Thank you.
Phong!
Ba!
Such a good decent job!
Oh my!
We should thank Hung for this.
Ba!
Should we give him a little commission?
You're good, Ba?
What happened today must be kept
as a secret until death.
Whoever spills the bean,
especially for Ut Det...
I'll kill him.
Are you out of your mind?
Who dares to reveal such private things?
Ta Dinh Phong! The customers called you.
Ok!
Ba, go with him.
Yes!
Hey, Ba, wait a second.
Could you go for me?
The customers want you.
Stay calm.
Don't worry.
Go make money to marry Ut Det.
You got this!
And you said we were best friends?
Friends my ass!
I'm sorry!
Get out!
Sir! Hey! Wrong room.
Long!
- Long!
- Wrong room.
Oh no grandpa! Wrong room! Oh my god!
Motherfucker, wrong room again!
Fuck you all!
Do you have any cigarettes left?
That's all we got. We must save.
Saving what? We earned a bunch of cash.
Here.
Hey, Ba!
Are you okay now?
I can barely breathe.
Why?
Wow, you lucky dog.
Stop teasing him!
You guys don't know.
She had smelly armpits!
And she held me so tight
she wouldn't let me go!
This is murder!
Why didn't you let Phong handle that
and you sing with those ladies instead?
Right.
No, she's kinky.
She has beard fetish, like me.
You have no beard.
Bullshit!
Let's get something to eat!
It's my treat!
Ok!
Long, I can barely breathe.
Just take it slow.
How are y'all doing recently?
We can't fucking do anything!
What was the problem?
Since you moved here...
they've been giving us shit!
How about moving to another place?
This place has been protected.
There would be more trouble
if I moved to the other place.
Sit here.
I'll make you two bowls of noodle soup.
We'll figure it out later.
You all conspire with each other!
Where's my money?
What money?
The money you robbed us!
- What are you doing?
- You hid in there, didn't you?
I didn't! I spent everything! Oh God!
Where's my money?
Where's the bag?
Where are Ut Det's shorts?
Where is it?
I have no idea what you're talking about!
I saw a rag cloth in the bike's glove box.
Is that what he means?
Where is it?
Damn it, where's the money?
- I told you it's gone!
- Gone what?
Where's my money?
Damn it!
Damn!
- Where's my money?
- How dare you turn it into rag cloth?
Stop it!
You're killing him!
Look at Ut Det's shorts!
How could they make it a rag cloth?
Long?
What?
How is it?
Is it enough?
Almost.
Maybe I'll make it next month.
Are you dying in there?
What are you doing?
You're gonna break the door!
Fuck!
What the hell?
Oh shit! I forgot.
My goodness!
Come inside with me if you can't wait.
Stop rushing me.
I forgot the door was cracked.
- Hey Phong!
- What?
We must find another way
to earn money quickly...
or Long's dad is gonna die
before we can make it.
I think Hung's place is okay...
just a bit...
…weary.
How about following him...
to join the Cho Lon gang?
It's faster that way.
No.
You know Long.
There's no way he would follow.
Oh God!
It's easy. We're gonna implore him.
I know he's really close to you.
Your turn.
The hell? You haven't flushed?
Get used to it, dude!
Did you use up all the toilet paper?
Use your shirt instead.
You are insane!
Stop! Stop running!
Stop right there!
Long!
Hello. What is it, mom?
Long?
I've got something to tell you,
Phong's mom…
What are you saying?
…she's in debt
and being hunted down by gangsters.
Give me a second, mom.
Mom, calm down.
Tell me what happened to Phong's mom?
Hey, Phong…
It's me, Phong.
What's wrong with my mom?
Your mom is in debt to the mafia...
they're hunting her down right now.
She's hiding in my place.
- Please do something.
- Alright.
Phong, calm down.
I'll think of some way to solve this.
They wanna kill my mom,
and you told me to calm down?
You're gonna go home by what?
I'll figure it out later.
What are you going to do
when you come home?
But I can't leave her alone there!
Okay, go.
Phong!
I've got an idea.
Have your friends replied?
I know them well.
They won't accept your offer.
You pay too much attention
to details while playing chess.
Damn you! I'm tired too!
Fuck you bastard!
I don't wanna lose a single piece...
even the weakest.
There are no weak pieces on a chessboard.
Advisor.
Even the Advisor...
has its own value.
Spare him!
Bastard!
I said spare him!
If you didn't tell them...
how could they know
where Big Brother hid?
Take him out!
Damn! Why did you stop me?
He won't say if we don't
beat the hell out of him.
I tell you this...
protecting Big Brother
is everyone's responsibility...
not your own.
Why did you keep it from us?
Why do you guys come here?
We wanna join the Cho Lon gang.
Are you out of your mind?
Hien...
Is your offer still valid?
The door is always open for you.
But first, we need your help on one thing.
Say it.
We need 50 million VND.
Immediately.
Hey kiddo...
do you think this is a bank or what?
On-demand all the time?
Fine.
But I also have one condition.